

# **ISAIAH OMONDI**

#### Contact Me

- **!** +254725711249
- isaiahomondi14@gmail.c
- MOMBASA ROAD Nairobi, Kenya



# Social Profile

- omondi isaiah
- mbori isaiah

# Other Info

# **Skills**

IT skills

marketing, sales,
Consulting,
Academic research
Mentoring and talent
development
Community service
Organizing exams
Teaching/ Training
programmes
Content Development
coaching



# **About Me**

To serve and work in an organization that encourages professional growth and where I can use my strong analytical, detailed and interpersonal skills along with exceptional common sense to improve services, in delight to my clients and inspire my clients while engaging in new challenges and learning new experiences.



# **Experience**

2020 - 2021 ARC Ride Kenya Ltd | Warehouse Supervisor/

Fleet Manager

Set up warehouse for operations
Recruit mechanics and drivers/riders
Oversee warehouse operations
Monitor and assist drivers in the field

2019 - 2020 New Light Secondary School. | Teacher

Class room teacher

Assist.learners improve their performance Incorporate technology in learning

2018 - 2019 Weston Commodity | Marketing

Sales of printers copy printers and photocopy machines to school

2016 - 2019 Testimony Secondary School | Teacher ( maths/ Physics)

# **Awards**

best teacher of the year best maths/ Physics teacher

# Languages

English, kiswahili,luo

# **Interest**

reading, idea Creation, personal growth, soccer, travelling,

# **Others**

isaiahomondi14@gmail.com

Class room teacher

Assist.learners improve their performance

Incorporate technology in learning

# 2011 - 2016 LandMark Concepts | Executive Manager

Manage the construction and distribution of Kevian

product

Expand the market in the region nationally

# 2016 - Eagles Solutions Consultancy | Director

Assist businesses achieve organizational purposes and

objectives

Solve management and business problems Identifying and seizing new opportunities

# Education

# 2004 - 2009 University Of Eastern Africa Baraton | B/Ed

UEAB people take on audacious problems, bring imaginative new approaches to solving them, and work collaboratively to advance knowledge and make meaningful and impactful contributions to our world.